Welcome to Psyche Awakens, a show in the panel verse where tarot, truth and raw conversation meet.
We explore boldly, we disagree intelligently and we protect the circle.
Here's how we roll.
House rules.
Debate ideas, not people.
No doxing, slander, hate or threats, ever.
Bring receipts, claims need sources or timestamps, no rumour relays, signal discipline, mix muted
and less called, no spam, no derail, the mods are the guardians, warning time out, ban,
no negotiations mid-show.
This is Psyche's channel, Psyche's Rules.
He keeps it safe, sharp and on topic.
Use common sense and be respectful to everyone and you will be fine.
Contribute or be entertained welcome if you're here to sow chaos hang out. There's a place for you here, too
Now welcome your host psyche see a storyteller and your host eTruth first shadows second
Let's get into it
you
So it's looking pretty good for me with what happened yesterday.
I got overcharged.
I didn't get overcharged.
Hey, burning joint, Nick.
What's up, Nick?
Hey, my microphone right here.
Does it look sound okay?
What?
I'm out of my priestly garb tonight.
I want to wash my, I pre-set it.
I think I got too sweaty in it.
That's Mr.
Tricks and where's Rudy?
Rudy's.
I really went outside to play, but oh, Mr. Tricks.
Oh, you're purring?
Are you purring?
You're a happy little cat?
He is purring.
Can you hear him purr?
You hear him?
Pick up the, hi.
Yeah, I wanted to address a couple things.
Let me see.
When I was on betas today, this woman named Katie.
I love you've seen this woman on beatus panel. She's there a lot. Um, I know Katie from like, you know last year
Um, I always got along fine with her
She started having problems with Jamie now
She's saying that I doxed her guys. Have I ever doxed anybody on my panel like I are my show never
Especially she's saying her full name her address. I mean, I love, you know, please dig up that clip
I'd love to hear that. I'm sure if I was to do that you could have and done a privacy
Privacy complaint against it. Why didn't you do that? I don't know and you said some other horrible things about me, too
Well, Christine, I apologize to get into Christine. She and I said, well, I think you've been watching my show because you mentioned
stuff that's been going on like
for example
You know that I've been replaying that a trip kit clip
Not even really about her was playing a lot of Chris K stuff out of it
But Chris K, you know, it's different than Christine Chris Chris K is like that
Mmm. He's peckerwood. Yeah, you you were friends Jamie, right?
And I was actually asking for Jamie up on the panel today. They're like, oh leave Jamie alone
Christine was like leave Jamie alone. Don't like
I was like, I'm friends with Jamie.
I knew Jamie before anybody here.
And she's like, well, I talk every day to Jamie.
Well, I talk every day to Jamie too.
And I've heard the whole story.
I tried to stay out of it,
but now I've been dragged into it.
And so I'm gonna defend myself.
No, I've never done what she said.
I'd never doxed her.
I never made fun of a,
she's saying I made fun of a six-year-old
on a, on Bronzeberg's panel.
A six-year-old who died in a fire or something like that and then she said I made fun of her
Second cousin's abortion. I don't know. I don't know anything about those things. I've never discussed anything like that
I just want to clear the air and you know clear my name
Also, I was on this woman or you know, Kate's panel Kate was perfectly nice to me
Barry was there. He was perfectly nice to me. There's this woman named Shannon. I don't I don't think she has a show
I heard I don't know if she's a streamer or
It's okay, Jamie. It's okay, you know, we knew this would happen, right? We knew it would happen
I should have addressed it sooner
She wrote me an angry text message. So she has my number, but I don't I didn't remember her. I don't know
But I'm not the kind of person to make fun of children. I'm not the kind of person to make fun of miscarriages or abortions or whatever
So I don't know what the F. She's talking about right?
but
That's enough, but anyway on Kate's show this woman was screaming about oh you live in a litter box
You know you got litter all over the floor, which I don't I have one litter box. It's very clean and
You know you're disgusting. I'm just like all these horrible things about me and actually Barry was like, okay
We'll give her a reading because she was like, oh, he doesn't know how to do tear
He doesn't know what the cards mean and stuff. I've been like I've been doing
Tarot since I was eight years old
So yes, I do and know what the cards mean and then I gave her a reading and it was a perfectly good reading
But then of course, what is she gonna give me like, you know, any any props or a thank you or anything? I know I
I thought I did a pretty good reading for her, but you know, she just wants to make fun of me and I
Did call her names because she called me names and
You know, maybe I was a little bit petty in that and not doing that
but
You know, and I don't usually like to do readings
Angry, but I still was able to give her a good reading. I
also
Kindly interpreted the car. I didn't like, you know, I mean first I said, oh, there's a I pulled the CUNT card
And you know it has a pair of face on or whatever, but that was a bad joke probably then I gave her a normal reading. Oh
I know Joe isn't it. It's terrible. It's terrible. I know but yeah, I called someone in name. Yeah
Oh
Then but tonight we had a good show we had flirty diamond returned and then we had you know auto on
auto is
Definitely in he wants to meet flirty diamond and I
Think she's a little bit too pricey for him, but
Come on up anybody that wants to come up. I'm not feeling a hundred percent. I'm like been really
Having some breathing problems today and not feeling a hundred percent and
Whoo, but I'm gonna try my best. Okay, so I'm
Welcome everybody. Oh 35 people in chat. Awesome. Hey, what's up everybody? Oh, here we come. We have a Mason the drummer coming up
Mason psyche. Hey, how are you? I'm sorry?
Thank you. Why was the channel going so crazy earlier? So why was everybody like going at it and stuff like that?
Oh because we had flirty diamond and you know auto on and it was it got pretty yeah
But psyche psyche that's not what it's supposed to be about. It's supposed to be felt people that just have a normal
Relaxed chill conversation. Well, I mean that's you might have seen that before but yeah, the show is about some fuck shit sometimes
You know, I try to keep it like a little bit kinder when you're around but you know
Can't always yeah diamond like earlier. Yes. Yes. Yes. So you talked to Natalie again
I mean when I was gone and stuff or what Natalie came up and said she thought flirty diamond was beautiful
I don't know if flirty diamond showed her hole. I don't know what that picture was
I think that was her belly button. Let's just hope it's her belly button
You like flirty diamond psyche
As a friend, as a friend definitely, you know, I'm not really like attracted sexually to transgender, but
She's a really cool person and she brought a lot of excitement to the panel verse, I think
You know when she came up. She said she was you know a natural woman and all these guys started falling in love with her
and then she
She admitted that you know, thank you. Why would you say all this weird stuff about like?
Auto needed a sperm like on on his face and stuff is that it went I thought auto wants to do that to well
I don't think she said that I think you know, maybe maybe
Maybe me or summer says something like that, but I'm not sure. Yeah, they weren't too far. So I keep what they said
well, you know
Diamond has a good sense of humor. And so, you know
Um, you know, it gets a little bit wild here sometimes Mason, I do want to protect you
But I don't think it was anything about you. Yeah. Oh, yeah
I'm not saying it's anything about me, I'm just saying I have to be make sure I'm not in it when there when it goes on because I need to be like safe right from right, but I think it was safe for you I mean I'm not going to let you like be picked on or anything.
You know I know you're autistic.
People with autism have pretty much a normal intelligence, right and yeah
But or above average intelligence, but it's like kind of focused on certain things
But I think you're smart enough to like handle it
I know it was a little emotional for you last night because people in the chat were kind of picking on you
So I want to talk to you. Yeah
It's like why would Joe say stuff about me they'll say it's I don't know he said something weird to me earlier
Like Joe would you say the Mason Joe what Joe don't need to spank you would you say the Mason come on?
You picked on Mason Joe
Psych he said something that was kind of out of line when Joe told me something early
Well, he's out of line with me too, but what do you say, you know exactly what he said? Oh
something like like
He said I look funny and I don't look funny psyche. He says, oh you look have a funny look at face. Oh my god
Joe, did you say he looks funny?
That's what Joe. That's what Joe told me earlier psych. Well, he's I think he's apologizing in the chat
It's not ass burgers Joe. It's as burgers and you know what?
People with autism should not just be made fun of you know, it's like we should respect that they might
Think a little bit differently, and you know what different is good. I'm I'm an abstract thinker
So I think differently too. So people think there's stuff wrong with me, too
Like what they said on on Kate's they're like, oh, yeah, he's not he's crazy. He's not all there
I'm thinking my beer making my second harder
Yeah
So it's like Joseph that flirty showed her whole I
Think it was just her man. He's talking about her mouth. I think
Right Joe, what were you or you saying?
It's called the well, yeah, come on up Joe you have to apologize to Mason, okay, and you come up and apologize to me
So I'll let you write up
Because you know what Mason you're a good guy. I had my suspicions. So I gotta do anything to deserve that
No, I'll just be myself. I think you know what? He's a jokester though
You know, he said things to me like I'm an f a gg ot if you know what that means and you know
He said horrible things to me too, but you know, he's a good guy
He doesn't mean it. He I think he has Tourette syndrome and he can't control his mouth sometime
Joe
Yeah, well, how's everybody in the chat? We have nice 47 people in chat
You know, I was at another show if you guys know tried and so I said when I talk to
So I can say when I talk to Jamie's Cowboys don't call that person a he it's a she like right? Yeah
Yeah, yeah, because Jamie's a Jamie's a beautiful woman and you're you're saying he and I think that annoyed her
Because you know we called he really so but you're learning still I don't think you meant it
Um, let's see, Joe wants it.
No, Syke, I didn't need it.
No, Syke, I didn't need it, though.
I know you didn't, Mason.
Oh, okay.
You're a good guy, Mason.
That was an accident, Syke.
People make accidents.
Hey, Joe's up here to apologize to you, by the way.
Here comes Joe.
I would never attack you Mason if it sounded like I attacked you. I apologize. I actually had to read like
I actually got like a bad case. It's red
Concealer
Think think clicker. I actually had like a bad case. It's rats. So but no, I never would ever attack you Mason
You actually look like my hero dime bag Darrell. Are you dying back there old junior?
Ass-legger!
Okay, oh my god.
The red's like, you know what?
The red's erected up again.
Ass-snickers!
Oh my god, yeah, I just can't rap amazing. I'm being silly. I would never fuck with your base and I mean that shit
I know I'll fuck around, but I would never fuck with your brother. You're a cool
I say jokes about like he can handle it. I know you're like you're cool, but I never will make fun of you, man
I thank you for turning that camera. Oh, because you actually were hurting my eyeballs
Cause like my eyes were like, like bleeding and they were like, ouch. Like,
do you see this? That's not a tear. That's blood coming out of my eyes.
So I'm going to leave now cause my eyes are bleeding,
but thank you for letting me come up here and apologize.
You're a real man.
So I keep it on Mason. Listen to me. Never would I attack you, brother.
You're a real man. You're a real man. All right. Thank you,
psyche. God bless you, psyche. Awake is thank you for letting me up here,
brother.
you're welcome. Thank you, man. I just wanted to hear you say you're welcome. God bless you.
Joe, we're cool, right? Joe, we're cool, right? You and I. Yeah, he said you're cool. You said
you're cool. Yes, you are cool, Mason. I love you. Peace. Okay. And so, Psyche. Yeah. But he said,
he said, I made his eyes bleed. How could I make his eyes bleed? So I don't understand. I think he was
then like any any guy he's gonna say that to so you only like he's gonna say that even about you you could say that about he's gonna say that about me
he says it all the time to me he says it all the time to me yeah and worse and worse things like that than that too
why aren't you a mod Joe can I trust you as a mod I don't know if I can
oh are you coughing
Yeah, psyche. I'm sorry, man. Oh, it's okay. You see my this DJ electric got me this bracelet. You see it's really cool
Oh, we have got a young guy. I don't want to talk to you
Saki, I didn't mean it. I don't mean for that. I know I know
So I had to have psyche I had to have that come out though. That's why I had to cough though
I couldn't help it. I had something like I had to cough up, you know, it's okay. It's okay. I understand Goddy. Are you there?
Yeah, I'm waiting for the host to greet me.
Oh, hello, Gaudi's on the show.
Hello.
Gaudi's on the show.
I need to start playing your intro music, which is, like, you know, the Gaudi song, but, um, yeah.
It's going on earlier and it you guys in a bad mood. I'm in a good mood
I'm a kind of a bad move because I got you know
There's a trial I forgot to cancel and then they tried to charge me $155 today
And that's a little bit too much and so and then they
Supposed to cancel that right after you sign up for I know I know I know I was a little bit drunk
And then I maybe forgot and or I thought I did and then they rejected my refund requests
That's the first time in like years and years and years. I had a refund request
Um, denied and so they're just like fuck you we're keeping the money and as they basically I don't know if it's for your subscription
Or if it's like for a month or whatever, but it's just 50 bucks for what?
It's uh, it's called a wonder share. It's kind of like I think they make clips of your videos and stuff
And so I mean if it turns out I can't get the refund. It's okay
I'll be able to like, you know, just use the service monthly and stuff like that if it's for one month
That's gonna be pretty ridiculous of a charge, but uh
But I would like a refund so I don't like, you know, have danger of overdraft fees and stuff like that this week
So I'm gonna I did a I did an appeal and then I appealed with PayPal too
They lied to PayPal and said that my subscription was still active. It's not I did cancel
With them within like, you know, 24 hours of the charge actually within like an hour of the charge
And so I don't really understand why the shady. Yeah, they're pretty shady with that
and you know, I don't want to call them out too much, but it's like
You know, it's kind of rude to, you know, deny the request.
That's going to cause me a lot of problems if they did.
Got it.
What?
Did you see that psyche turn into Father's psyche?
That's what his name is now on here.
Yeah. Oh, I didn't see that.
Yeah, I am. Oh, yeah, I see it now.
I'm not in my priest costume, but I can wear my, my sash or something.
I have this.
He's a Padre.
I don't know.
God he turned into a pod right now. Yeah, he's like father psyche and now he's a Padra. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, and I had a bad time. I mean, I didn't have a horrible time at Kate's because I did make five bucks
And that's always cool. Thank you Barry the turtle for donating for a reading
But people were really mean about my reading. Oh, you don't know how to do Tara and I got everything right, you know
It's like I they actually said oh well
That's what this is what this card means and that's exactly literally the words that I said were even on the card
And so I don't know how I got it wrong, but you know
if they want to slander my tarot abilities, they want to call my house a litter box, they are welcome to you because I know the truth that it is not
that's your fault, you know that, right?
why? because I told too much, I expedite
no, because you hang around people that hate you
I know, but you know what? I can't help it, some people just hate me, do you see this? do you see that?
so like, what is that? what are you trying to show?
yeah, that's Mohammed
It's not it's not Mohammed. That's it's either sandal thaw or metatron. Oh
Metatron. Oh, yeah, the guy who writes all the shit down. Yep. Yeah, and then I has the back
It has the 72 names on it. That's all Hebrew right there. I also have this one. This is something else. I got it. It's pretty cool
This is yet there
See that's a four leaf clover
these are kind of symbols adapted from the Solomon seals and
You know, I do notice that
Lot of cool stuff has happened since I started wearing these but I won't go too much into magic
You know what I'm gonna do. I'm gonna send you a rabbit's foot. Oh, thank you. I
Don't mind do you?
No, as long as there isn't it's not it's not like fresh. It's that's yeah, it's gonna be fresh
Oh, no, I don't want that. That's the luckiest one man. Oh fatal attraction. Did you boil?
I'm gonna send you the whole rabbit
You are or not? Oh, no, just the foot. Okay. Did you eat the rabbit? You want to you want all four you just want the one
I don't need four. I just maybe just one is fine. All right one's enough. Let's make a necklace out of the four now
Watch somebody's gonna send you a bloody rabbit's foot and then it's gonna be my fault. It will be your fault
I'm gonna I'm gonna report report you to the authorities for that. Don't kill rabbits people. No
Yes, what?
Hey guy, did you see that somebody named auto in here earlier?
There's a guy named auto talking to flirty diamond. They were going at it with each other. Yeah, they were flirting with each other
Yeah, I saw that
I think they were flirting with each other. Yeah
Yeah, he's into that. That's pretty good. Yeah, that's good. He doesn't discriminate
Well, you know, he does
You know, he came out of the closet. I got on my show. I mean, should I be insulted because he said he would never
Hook up with me with me and then now he's all interested in Flirty Diamond. He was lying. He was lying to you. He's lying
Okay, yeah, he's Canadian, you know
They do that. Oh, yeah, he's he's in Canada. Hey, he's in India. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, they wouldn't let him in the US. So we had to go up there
well
You know, he's a swim real extra to get to Vancouver
And God if you do want your I don't give a channel God II or no
Yeah, fake channel that I use just to come on here. Okay. Yeah. Well, if you ever do start your channel
I can put you on the psyche verse if you go to psyche
Okay, go ahead. Go ahead. Why would you have a fake channel? Why would your channel be fake for?
Because I don't use the channel
Yeah, but you can use it though. God. He just he's got to use it to do what?
You know videos what kind of content what content am I gonna make?
You can what am I gonna do? What am I gonna make some little videos of me doing little dances? Yeah
Guys, that's gonna be fun. Everybody wants to see that gaudy dancing dancing
Yeah, can you do a tiktok dance? I'm gonna monetize myself dancing 24-7. I'll also subscribe
I'll just make a loop video for an hour. You just guys watch it 24-7. I'll leave the chat open monetize it
Let's do it. Look at my teeth. Look pretty good. Got you, huh? Yeah, what you get bleached? No, dude
It is this is just natural teeth. How do you get dirty ass fucking fingernails and you get the great teeth?
I have a great dentist or great dentists
Yeah, my finger nails are gonna dirty today, but this one's good. No, no, I'm not looking at those the teeth are great
Yeah, well, thank you. I do have nice teeth and they're not like everyone that says oh my god
He's horrible. Like I have nice teeth actually the straight the only thing straight about me is my teeth by the way
Yeah, you got blessed with good teeth
Thank you. Actually, they would be a mess without a good orthodontist
Nobody can say that you're a meth addict
Right because look at my teeth like this. Oh my god. Who is that horrible? Isn't that horrible? Who is that?
That's mason's mom. No, come on
Like he's like he said like you said that he really said
You have a good sense of humor
You gotta fucking laugh at your mom, bro
Wow
You did I found it funny that you thought it was funny and that so you have a good sense of humor
So I appreciate that you know, I'm gonna cry don't don't be one of those people that cries all the time
I mean nobody wants to hear that
Well Mason maybe cried a little bit last night, but people in the chat were mean to him and can you cry Mason? Did you cry?
No, God, I didn't cry bit
All right, good. You just his eyes his cheeks were wet a little bit. Let me find out you were crying on panel, dude
the
Yeah, you never cracked a joke on a real
Yeah, you got to do that. What does that mean Goddy like I don't understand that means you don't you don't have a sense of humor I
Never made a joke is what you're saying. No, I never heard you make a joke
Is that true this was true
So you never made a joke I
Can't think of any jokes Goddy. That's why I don't say any joke. Hey
You see
I mean, I think I've heard of some some some cow jokes. Let me see if I can find a cow joke
I'll make me I'm gonna try to make Mason laugh. Let me see you like cow jokes Mason
Yeah, we're cow go to get entertained Mason, you know we're a cow goes to get entertained
They went to the farm, right?
Went to the movies.
Okay, that's that.
What's in the movies?
It's like.
What do you call a cow that just gave birth?
A cow, a cow, right?
No, you call it decaffeinated, decaffeinated.
Oh, wow.
Decaffeinated, what?
Hey.
It's like, how's it decaffeinated?
Why would it, why don't you get it?
Because a calf is like a baby cow,
and so it's D, which means like a cat,
it gave a birth to a cow, so it was decaffeinated.
How about what do you call a cow with a sense of humor?
Oh, like I don't know it's like laughing stock. Oh
Hey now
Laughing stock. Okay. Why do cows wear bells? Anyone know why do cows wear bells?
Because they jingle bells, right?
As their horns don't work. Oh
Because their horse don't work. Hey Mason, do you know what do you call a cow jumping on a trampoline? No
a milkshake, a milkshake, a milkshake, because it's shaking, it's on the trampoline.
Mason, what do you call my ex-wife, a whore, oh, sorry about that, I'll see you later man.
What do you call?
Hello, nobody's gonna live. I just call my ex wife a whore. Nobody's gonna live.
It's not very nice.
Fuck all of you.
Oh, you two always smile.
Do you see a wife?
He said wife.
He's got it.
You didn't find that funny?
You said a wife?
When he said that?
He was married
You know what a cow's favorite can do you say Kim? Oh shit, you didn't say Kim. What's the cows favorite candy?
Who knows what this chocolate psyche a milky way? Oh
Hey, come on
What do you call a cow with no legs? Oh?
I don't know
ground beef. Ground beef? It's like ground beef. Yep. What do you get from a spoiled cow? A pampered
cow. You get milk. Spoiled milk. Spoiled milk comes from a pampered cow. Spoiled milk. What's
a cow's favorite subject in school? What?
English Calculus Calculus Calculus Calculus
Yeah, that calculus and one more one more calculus. What do you call a cow sleeping in a field?
Amanda a bull dozer. Oh my gosh
Doze that when you sleep it's called dozing I want one more actually
What why did the cow cross the road?
Cuz trying to get to the other side to get to the other side other other side or the other
Yeah, so I was one more. I knew that one. Yeah, you got one. Gotty give us one more. Oh, you want one more?
Okay, I got another joke. Let's see
What do you get when you cross an angry sheep with them in a moody cow?
What
a cow that's in a bad I'm sorry. I asked. I'm sorry. Sorry, everyone. Oh, thank God.
Canada drives here to save the family. Oh, kid. What up, kid? What's going on, psych?
Long time no see, man. Thank you, Canada, for not being hard on me on that
And we see a girl. Can we see a girl before we get started with this whole conversation there. Oh, there she is. Hi. Hi, sweetie pie.
Oh, she ran. She ran. We saw her. Yeah, she got a little shy. She got a little shy.
Yeah, she was shy on the Bronzebergs panel. Very sweet girl. Very sweet girl.
Sorry, go ahead. Go ahead, guys. Go ahead.
Mason, what do you call a pig that knows karate? Amanda.
I don't know. It's like, what is it?
Um, anybody know what you call a pig that knows karate a pork chop pork chop. That's good
Your anus. No, no, no. Oh pork chop. There it is. Oh, yeah, he got it a pork chop
Pretty good. So yeah, you just went up there and you know, address Christine. So that was fine. Thank you
So what what is a cow like it? What is the cow that knows?
I
Yeah, they're getting up on me. I
I'm not a big
mean fuck Christine every day all day but I apologize to Christine today and I
said I'm sorry and she said I do not accept your apology and so oh she's a
stink fish don't worry about it stink fish you heard the man stink fish yeah
no I I I only have direct like if I'm having an issue with someone I'm gonna
because I thought I I mean I you know we had a little we had issues before but
it's like I think we worked through our issues and that's cool but I don't
know some people just won't forget are not
like Jesus if someone apologizes be like Jesus and like say you know forgive
and be forgiven and stuff like that you don't like let someone apologize and
say not not you're not forgiving God it's easy to forgive just do it God right
Talk to Gotti and then say Gotti. I'm sorry for everything. I all my sins and Gotti will forgive you, right?
They say God forgives. That's not true. Oh
Are you gonna forgive me? I don't forgive but you can forgive. It's very easy
Um, where is everyone at tonight anyways? Well, I don't know. I mean we have 50 people in chat. That's pretty awesome
We had like 75 or 70s. I believe earlier almost 80 people and that was awesome
That's cuz flirty diamond and an auto were just tearing up the panel verse with you know
Auto being attracted to flirty diamond and wanting to make love to flirty diamond be made love, too
I mean he wanted it in anal leave from flirty diamond. I mean that sounds like people would pay a dollar a month to watch your show
Wow, yeah, it was it was pretty pretty pretty scary
Sounds like lost not love. It was content though. Here's what really was content, right? It was great content
Yeah, you know, we can all forgive. Just not you got it. Oh, yeah, give me. I don't need your forgiveness
Well, God is a cool. Do you know Goddy pretty well Canada
Remember the time we were talking about watches and I wasn't listening
Yeah, that's most of the time I'm talking about watches. No way back
His girlfriend's laughing right now because she knows all about the watches and they say making fun of they're even making fun of Canada
Dry last night saying you know, but his glasses and stuff like please
I mean, it's like come on. He is my glasses are fire. I don't give a fuck. Yeah, he has cool glasses. He's my helmet
What do you know about my helmet? That's my lighter me my lighter. Jamie's talking about my helmet
Yo, Alex, what's up, buddy?
Oh, yeah, Alex is awesome guy and I want to thank everybody. I did I did get you know a lot of people have issues with mr. McQueen and
Not me, you know, we've always gotten along. He's always been respectful even when he's given me shit. I'm like, this is just McQueen
I think Alex is doing this thing. He's he's being McQueen Alex is being Alex, you know, it's because you're Canadian
He'll be a bad for you. He doesn't mean harm. He doesn't mean any harm really
Well, you better feel bad for me buddy. My country's getting taken over. Yeah, man. You're gonna lose your guns soon
Fuck we're gonna lose not just our guns, but our fucking land and our integrity too
Well, you know what cannon dry
Just come move to the US. Just make just say you know the US will we won't give you health care, but we will
You know probably move in with psyche
We can't hey, we have Ziggy on the panel Ziggy's coming up. It's about time. Yeah. Well, he was here last night God
He came back last night, so
Ziggy oh, hey, what's up guys? How you guys man? I just want me to move in. Did you see how fast he changed the subject there God?
Yeah, never mind. I already have Q living here. It's a little bit crowded. Yes, that's not gonna go. Well, yeah, he already maced me
You actually have a roommate right now psych. I don't I have didn't call you an end my cats are my roommates
But they call you an end when he based you or an F. Call me then and the n-word. He said the
N-word and I can't have mace in my face. I just didn't call you the F. I know I know
But no, I heard he's actually like living with some man in Beverly Hills. My right or am I wrong?
Victor Sakis, okay?
Yeah, he's found a sugar daddy. So, you know, I think he's happy Beverly Hills from a tent to Beverly Hills
He's a pool boy. What was it? Was it was it maize or was it bear spray? Um, did you see did you see that Ziggy?
He may sit down in a tent
Yo mad daddy is over at money for 20s right now. I haven't seen mad daddy in forever. Well
Hey, Money420, you are on the Psycheverse website.
I don't know if I have it handy.
I can show you the Psycheverse website.
I have other people on it too,
but I'm still working on updating the website.
Let me see if I can pull them off.
You good money, you're good, eh?
Yeah, we're good. I mean, I put them on the psyche verse. So obviously I do want to help them out
Let me see. Or because it's psyche verse org
It's still under construction, but I do have it is coming up when I do psyche verse or here
It is right now and share the screen and you know, I thought I'd do like a friendlier kind of IP to style
Website so here it is. What do you think?
Yeah, I mean so so here's what's live and look there's money for 20
Traveling it's nice heroes on there. Yeah, it's your ish summer's channel
IRL news time some of Alexander's channel on my channel. I also have pages on there, too
If I go like um to see all streamers. I don't see you on there
Beat is not on there right now, but I'd be happy if I make up with Beat. I'll be happy to put her on there
But yes, actually, it's not updated yet
But yeah, there were but I put page on there too and your DG Electra's channels and who else I put on
Somebody
And, you know, and if you guys want to be on it too, just let me know and I can add you, but it's I have to do it slowly a little bit I put a lot of money into it and so, but it's going to be a cool website and I look forward to having like it will tell when the streamers on and we'll have a list of like when they're on and stuff like that.
I don't know like people maybe they already have IP to so if they're on IP to that's that I want people that are up and coming streamers or streamers that I've met on this show and stuff like that to help promote them and stuff I do want to make up with beta I actually did text messenger a couple times today she's still she's still mad why because
The bottom you don't want to have the heart at the bottom of my heart. I still I still do love her
That's who that's who's like he is. He's a guy that forgives. I
Know I can't be mad at it's like I even if I'm mad at somebody like really pissed like the next day
I wake up and like feel bad if I say say means
What would be the worst thing that she could do to you?
For you to never forgive her. It would be something like, you know, like suing me or the cats or something
Oh, yeah, or like, you know, same mean thing
She was like, I'll send you manure. She did she did threaten me
Well, I don't know if she threatened me about that. So I'm gonna just let that one go. But
Yeah, she shouldn't be I don't think I think those are kind of empty threats about like suing people because it's like, you know
When you're honest go
You're a public figure when you have a show on YouTube.
So if you say something on your show.
Yeah, you got to enter it.
You got actually talked about on a show the other day.
Oh, I heard I was really badly talked about too today,
like earlier, but then she was like.
Badly? Really?
Was I?
I am not the one that I saw.
Was it her show or what?
No, no, it was Jesse.
What the fuck?
Aw, man.
I've never heard of it, Jesse.
I don't like Jesse's adventures or something. I wish that I was Jesse's girl. Jesse's adventures
Something I can't know. That's not it. I'm it's wrong. It's that a bagpiper. Goddy. Who's that? No, that's me
No, no, that's you. That was me. Yeah, you're not like you know, I was a green beret. Oh green beret
But why is it red? Well, they call it green
Oh, okay. Are you the part of the Guardian Angels?
Well, he's like referring to...
Jesus Christ. Why are you bringing up the Guardian Angels for?
Because I know that guy. He was on Fox News all the time.
That crazy Guardian Angels guy.
That boy, that guy was a douchebag, huh?
He wears that fucking beret all the time.
Yeah. He never takes it off.
He wears the beret.
It looks like the Indian Hopkins.
Yeah. Is that sign on for the lambs?
I can see it.
Bah, he's gonna be the next mayor in New York
He's gonna have guardian angels all over the place
I'm gonna I'm a loudmouth lamb if I get taken to the
Whatever it is the slaughterhouse. I'm gonna fucking ah my head off. You know
That was like you lost a lot of people man
Let's be real about this. You lost a lot of people. What's at a 67 in my chat right now
How many people did I lose and I think you lost about a hundred people over the last four months for some reason
Well, because they're all in bronze birds like those like those hundred hundred sour bitter beddies like whatever
So they were his friends more than they were yours. You gotta think you gotta think got and got a you got to think man
Beat is over there like don't go to don't go to don't go to psyches
If you go to psyches, then you're a piece of shit I know and then she's like oh, he's uh, you know, he's
He's a bad person. No, I don't know what I don't know what she said
But she was saying don't donate the psyche and stuff like that
Well, she's been saying that for months though
It's like I mean come on and then now she does doing the clapping system too plus
I tried to go on our show today and I can get one word out like over a Bronzeberg screaming at me
It's the third time this happened and everyone in the chat was like let's psyche talk like let's go one-on-one
No, she, she, I don't know, okay, I wasn't there, but probably even her own people, people
are like, they're not about it anymore.
And they're probably, I'm just guessing you can only say it, but probably her own people
are like, let him fucking talk, Jesus fucking Christ.
I know even girls hate was like oh my god
She's like Bronzeberg ruin the stream because he's shouting over me and then it's like she's screaming at me a high-pitched voice
She's like I understand why psyche is being a bitch over there because it's like it's can't even like get a word out
But you know, I'll admit that it's okay if you can call me you can call me whatever man
I don't give a fuck God. He's on your side. I'm on your side fuck her. She's a bitch. You know what she did to me
What?
She fucking went to my woman
Posted on her shit that you need to take care of Ziggy. He's out of out of Lane or something
She didn't even she's not bad. He's out of lane. Wait, you know, she's not bad. Who's your girl?
I never fucking right out of Lane. Hey, hey Ziggy. Do you look like an emo?
I saw a picture you look like you're in the Banggood Charlotte or something like that
That was your picture that they put him on a fuck
Yeah, that wasn't me at all.
Yeah, it was actually me, of course.
The one that was kissing Bader, right?
Well, no, no, well, I think JT put that up or something,
but it was on her show, it was like some emo guy,
like he had like black hair, like what the fuck now?
That wasn't you?
Everyone was like, that's an emo, he's emo,
and I was like, I don't know if that's him.
No, that was said, that baggade,
Rob, fucking, what's his fucking name?
Black lipstick on?
Gotti.
Rob, the slob, big Rob slob.
Yeah, Zinny's Rob was trying to,
he didn't have pictures on me.
So he chose your picture.
You have your dermal piercings, Piggy?
What's that?
You got some dermal piercings?
Nope.
No, you guys want to see a picture of Ziggy. I got a picture of Ziggy. Hold on. I want to see what he looks like
So put it up. Hold on here it is
On your ship before dude, there he goes
Is that you oh my god, you're black. I know you're black. Yeah, you know
Yeah, he's black
Oh, is that a problem?
No, he's into weird shit, I don't question that he's the tomato is a case that it looks like the guy from many
If you on say he was a part of his name, but he was like this like
Listen listen psyche what they did was is that that that Rob guy he hates that Bader guy, right?
So he made
He went and found your picture because he didn't have a picture of me
Oh, baby, and he threw me up. No, not Vader
Rob big King Rob or whatever. Oh, oh, yeah, but but Rob actually picking Rob
Who was actually like some like six foot eight sexy Samoan? He looks like a five foot two like Mexican?
He's not yeah, right. I'm gonna go eat a Greek salad, you know that guy. Yeah
Here it is. He's like this is Ziggy and it's you buddy's asshole just fluttered
That was, um, Gotti's Gotti. Thank you. Thank you
No, no, so so it was funny because he did a video for Vader and
it's like Vader and then fucking
it was like
The title was like Ziggy and Vader lovers or something or whatever
And then I'm like, okay, I want to I want to see this click
And then it's you and fucking Vader turning to each other and fucking kissing and I'm like, why didn't he use my fucking picture?
Vader never kissed me. Vader, I tried he turned his head away, so I
Tried kissing Vader. You're going to work Alex
Alex is putting on his police uniform.
I want to see it, just put your police uniform,
just the button like neck down, Alex.
I want to see your police uniform.
I really want to see it.
It's better not be a janitorial costume.
He's putting on his-
You guys ever see Alex?
Yes, I have because he actually
Yes, like he's the only person who's ever seen Alex. This is the picture that psyche psyche. Oh my god
Yeah, that's Alex Alex Alex NYPD. Yeah, so her got so mad. She didn't believe him. He's a very happy guy
He is he is Alex is a happy happy guy. I love Alex. Alex is a good guy
People are like, oh fuck Alex. I'm like Alex was there for me when I needed him
You know and you know done some stuff good stuff for me behind the scenes and stuff
So and then no, they didn't whoever was on the panel of beat is they didn't do do that for me
So, you know when I needed them and so
I don't know Christine was very mad at me today too and you know, oh fuck psyche
You know psyche just wants people to stand up for him
I you know I would stand up for you psych but I'm in the wheelchair, so
I want God to sit down for me
Is a sense of humor that's what I like about Goddy
He's like man
I take I take all the things that have went wrong in my life and
Alex you have to talk sorry
It's out. It's it's it's a it's actually like an alchemy. You know some alchemy like I do I turn the shit into like gold
That's what I do. It's like and who else can do that? Yeah
Like God he doesn't like well, I'm learning
God he's still teaching me. Well, he's the host of the shows that y'all that he gets all the shit
Alright, well, we don't get all the shit
We just get this stuff that splatters off of him, but he gets all the piles of shit
Who wants a tarot reading this group? I can do terrible. It's a tarot. Yeah, go ahead
Give us give us one. I got one. I'm gonna shuffle a little bit. The who ones went gaudy or give us the reading
Diggy wants one no do one for do one for Canada drives girl
Canada drives do no actually can I have a request? Yeah
Can you do one four?
We're in the chat oh
The only one they have to be here. I want them to be here so I can get consent
I do for Canada drives girl. Okay. Can I drive? Can I give one to your girlfriend?
Yeah, yeah, she doesn't want a reading. Okay, do you want to ask her if she's gonna be lucky and love?
No, she didn't want one. Can I take one? Okay, he'll take one. Okay, so I got can of dry. Okay.
Okay, can of dry. Okay, got that got that.
Look and see if she's gonna find love anytime soon. I'm just doing a five card reading. Okay, and then okay.
and
Okay, okay, so here's what I got for Canada drive Canada driver side of the page of swords
This is what I call like the spy car
And so I don't know if you've been spying or somebody's been spying on you
But there's been somebody maybe watching you in the past maybe kind of in a nicer way seeing it
I want to see what my girlfriend's fucking spying on you. Yeah, I think
I don't know who the other two guys
Everybody says featuring
Let me see, I can't really, let's see, featuring curiosity.
and basically just spying terms.
But then I see like you are in this King of Pentacles energy
like right now or it's like the man that has everything
that's what it says right there.
So you've got everything.
It's like, and you're also able to manifest good things.
And I also see you're working with some other people maybe
or you will be working with some other people.
There's a couple of people that have been watching you
maybe to see your progression and they're interested.
They're impressed with your progression.
That's interesting.
Also, see maybe you watch out for like some kind of heartbreak. I'm not sure what this is
It is the three of swords and the three of swords is usually
With a black dude and it says
the
It is. They're old horror movies. It's called the whore deck and uh yeah and so you got but
you got this magician power and it says he holds the power of all the elements in the palm of
his hand and so you know how to like work with the elements in order to get what you want and so
you'll be able to get past any heartbreak or a sad moment and stuff like that and yeah and so
People watching to wanting to work with you and stuff and really impressed with your progress
Maybe a heartbreak coming up, but also the ability to get out of it and then manifest what you want
So I hope you like that reading. Wow. Thanks psych. That one was pretty good. You're welcome
Yeah, I mean it's like that this woman tonight was just like
I scared you with the three of three of swords or you scared me with the three of swords
Yeah, but you know what we all have these heartbreak moments and it's like I but also it's maybe a warning and that that maybe help you to prevent that you know it's like
Just you know be prepared for
Anything to happen, right?
So, uh, yeah, I got that. I got my pineapple of strawberry. Oh, we have mason back here comes mason on the panel
Did you get some new rings psyche? I did I shall show you one second. Here we go
There you go
Not cool, man
Yeah, what's a pentagram and one's like a gem like a kind of a greenish purplish psyche. Yes. Yes
Do I really make Joe's eyes bleed like Joe's like my eyes are bleeding now fine. He's fine. He was just kidding. He was just kidding
you know he's a jokester mason don't don't take it don't take it to heart okay
but psyche psyche how would i make his eyes bleed just by looking at me and psyche his eyes would start bleeding
maybe
you said they don't know but
he did but i think he would have said that
he was just kidding what kind of person says that to another human being
i know joe you're in big trouble joe
joe wants to spanking it
who's like joe who
Joe blow breaking up
Yeah
How could Joe how could Joe be so mean to me? God, you know what it is
Mason, you know what it is he grew up a ginger and when you grow up a ginger people who really tease you a lot
You know and he became an adult so he tries to mask it with humor
Yeah, but it's still deep inside his brain
And he's still that little kid that everybody picked on and not to mention gingers don't have a soul
So, you know what they used to call him when he was a kid
I'm Chuckie no bloody Mary bloody Mary bloody Mary. Oh, that's how that's how they called him
Because back then they used to call little sissy boys Marys
So because the red hair they call him bloody Mary bloody Mary bloody Mary. Hey, you just made her appear stop it
Yeah, she just appeared on the show
Bloody Mary God he doesn't make any sense got it because I didn't do anything for him to say that
Traumatized people cut deep Mason. It's a problem. This is Lilith Scorpiana, and you're watching psyche awakens TV
TV is a portal to the shadows of the soul
Illusion and transformation demands courage
The veil of the soul dragging you into the abyss where raw truth claws at your core
It's a relentless point into that only the brave emerge
There's just what she's gonna do with that tail. She's gonna sting you with it
She sounds tired
She is a little bit. She oh, she's tired and bored
That's what she gets when talking to me for hours, you know, she gets bored. She's like, oh, it's like not another commercial
You're gonna make me do that was a bloody Mary actually, but
Donald Trump now we turn into Donald Trump got it. That's why I fit your Donald Trump. Oh, it's my boy
My president
He voted for him. He's the best. Yeah four times. Oh my four times. He only ran twice. Yeah, okay
Well, hey, there you go in the primaries to
He ran three times genius. You just you just you just doxxed yourself at least had four
But you just doxxed yourself because now we know you live in New Hampshire
How's that work
because that's what you live in New Hampshire. Oh, you can vote twice in New Hampshire? Okay, yeah. Yeah, I live in New Hampshire.
The population of New Hampshire. Let's narrow it down here. I've docked myself. Nice. How many mil, I think. A few mil? How many mil?
Yeah, don't come looking for me. Oh, gosh. Yeah, you guys are cool as hell. Diggy, you're not mad at me?
No, I'm not mad at you. You were talking about one of my buddies though. Just a while ago, man
I think I'm gonna download your brain. Who's mad at me
No, you were mad at somebody in the chat. Oh, I was gonna know I was mad at anybody in the chat
I was mad at this woman named Shannon that was on the redhead
Shannon you're talking about Shannon
Well, there's another couple Shannon, so don't get the wrong one, but there's another there's no the redhead
You were mad at the redhead. I'm I'm not trying to put words out. Who's the redhead Donald Trump?
It's a guy. No, it's a guy ginger from the Gilligan's Island. Ginger. Right. Ginger was a drag queen. I'm sure she
No, she was it was Tina Louise. I miss my girl Tracy. She's still alive. Well, Tracy's mad at me
She was at the at the yes, she is
I think so. Let me see if she died.
Is Tracy mad at you?
Tracy is mad at me still.
Tracy was in the haters club meeting.
Is she?
Yeah. She was mad about...
I made a song that...
I said in the song that Michael paid her back
or left her money in the wheel or something.
Did he?
No, he didn't.
I know she's mad about that.
So I keep.
Yes.
Tracy we're talking about X like Tracy. No, no, no the other the black Tracy the african-american
I don't know that I what about X Tracy though. He was here a night earlier
She and I are friends again. Like that's one break. Did you get it?
Saki, did you get it? I sent you you send me would you send me another out episode?
Oh look, oh look
Yeah, there's like, I said to you something like I said to a video.
There's a phrase that David and Michael passed away.
Do you know Michael passed away, um, Canada Dry?
Yeah, buddy, I was here when we all figured it out.
Did he?
Yeah, he did.
He passed away.
How, how did he win?
Fuck off, God.
You were here too.
God, he said that he...
I don't know if it's true.
Yeah, he was depressed.
He was depressed and you guys piled on him.
I didn't pile on him.
He was an asshole, though.
Don't tell me you guys pushed it on him.
He was a big asshole, that guy.
He was, but no one deserves to...
Yeah, well, he did.
It was his choice.
I'm not being a dick, man, but you guys didn't like...
It was his choice. Come on.
Push on it or something. I don't think I don't know if he did that
I know he might have had heart problems and stuff like that or something like you know, but maybe Myra killed him. Oh my gosh
I'd be a never know. I don't want to say a little bit. I told you she was jealous of you
Insecurity issues a little bit, but I bet by the way, I did know Michael probably like April of last year or April
We're mayor something. I met him on Benny's show. I was on a panel
So I knew him longer than anybody else and he was always supportive of me on this show
I knew him longer than anybody else in the show at least like by the way
Somebody donated $200 to his go fund me for his casket. Was it you?
That wasn't me, but that's very nice of them to do. Did you donate? I didn't even know he had to go find me first cast
That would come up here he I think he used to be at TPB and then he started coming up here
He was like lawn
Loud and he'd be in his bedroom all the time with like yes in the back. Yep. Yep
He was in love with psyche and he had he said he had a girlfriend with jealous of the whole relationship
Yeah
He was a cool guy. I hope he faked his death
He did
That's why I'm packaged was late
Yeah
Well, well Michael he was a good guy God bless RIP Michael
I'm not gonna play the Michael song again because it has that lyric in it. So unless I change the lyric
I don't know. There's a Michael song
there was but it said I didn't know he donated he said he gave Tracy it left Tracy $800 in his will but
it was an 800 it was it was zero it was zero
oh shit so uh
Jesus
people got kind of mad
People got kind of mad, and I don't think he had a will.
I'm not sure.
Mike still owes Tracy $800.
$800, yeah.
He owed her $800 the whole time.
God damn.
And he was like, I'm never paying it back.
And I was like, I really hoped it would be a plot twist that he did.
And I was just sorry.
I just like.
I now have more questions.
She's going to have to get it from his grave.
Mike, I have more than $800 out of Tracy.
We can like, if they dig him up, they can take his rings or something like that.
She's going to have to go to hell to get it.
No, how did.
how did Michael get that money from Tracy in the first place he said he was he said he was gonna
dive or like you know have you know he said he was gonna get shake start shaking from alcohol
withdrawal or something and he needed a case of beer he sent her pictures of his dawn and she fell
Like what's Tracy doing? Does she have money to? Can we drag money?
She could always clap them from the panel like and that's why she's gonna miss her big pipes is here. Oh, wow
This is great. Yeah
My wish came true
Big pipes, what do you think about Alexander coming out to see me?
I want 800
You wrote a song about it
It's been a couple of years
Bring Tracy out here
Come up, you're welcome
I just want to hear my fucking response
What is anal clamp?
I don't have that programmed in
I don't have anal clamp in yet
So you have to butt plug or butt hold
That's all I have
TPP you asked me a question. Okay. I'm sorry. Go ahead
Yeah, he gets kind of nerdy dude
Big pipes. What's the answer to the question? You're happy to see that true. Yeah, I thought it's great
I
Thought it was great to experience
Alexandria as a real woman and you know as a real human real woman. You matter. Have you met her?
No
She did say I think she did say that she doesn't want to meet you someday though, you know, so what's an anal clamp?
We it was supposed to happen like we had we had planned several times in the past over the years, but they never
They never they never actually conspired, right?
But
Show them your biggest quality man like dude this guy can play a harmonica and play guitar at the same time banjo banjo
Maybe you can banjo. That's right. Correct. He doesn't go on cam anymore. He doesn't he's been off cam for like three months
Yeah, do it now. Do it now. I haven't seen you in a while. I went on cam like
Thank you money for 20 last night
Go to a psyche verse org and I listed you there, okay, cuz I want to support you okay, so
That's what I'm saying like do it. I know you play guitar do it for a fuck off you
I always thought when Michael died like it was horrible. No, I really mean it. I always thought it was like a horrible April Fulcher
This one's by Nirvana, but then when I found out he was actually dead. I was like, yes
Hell yeah, thank God. No, Joe. Come on. Don't talk about that. Thank God he's dead
This son, I got to thank God you heard him right here. Yeah
Turned out. He's got me fucking turned on like a lecture got me this
Thank you light up light of your lighter for big pipes. There you go
Little bit a little bit
No, I got it. I got it. I can turn
I like you. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it. You can do it
It's perfect. It's perfect.
I like your jewelry, Sikes. Thank you.
I think I look better than you. I don't remember that. If I get you a Jewish shirt, will you wear it?
Yeah, Yamaha. No, no, no, like a rabbi hat.
This is a teen spirit
Black hole sun
won't come
and wash away the rain
glass world sun
won't you come
hold on a minute
I thought it was a matching pumpkin
it's the behind the scenes
Electra, Electra, I also put you on the website and she's going to take a look at your update.
What should he do?
Take a look at him.
He's really good.
Electra, look at this.
Electra, check this out.
Drive me insane.
What do I got?
Electra, it's not up yet, but it will be still.
Here, take this out.
Electra, look.
Hold on, do you see it?
Hold on.
There, I got you on there.
Do you get Electra's drive?
Do you get Electra?
And I got it hacked by the videos.
I made it for fuck's sake, then I...
I think I got it right.
Is the website being called?
Psyche, I made a mistake, didn't I?
Psyche burst off the road.
That's not what it is.
I don't even believe the damn, the car or what the fuck.
Okay, yeah, I got a specific order.
Traveling Disney, money for 20 or that?
Can you marry him?
Can you mute Psyche? Can you mute him?
This is crazy.
Oh, you can put a hand up there, like, killing clown.
Torture clown.
Jesus website right now. That is so crazy. I've been working on this website. It's not ready yet
It's gonna have a directory in there with your name in it. He's he'll be alright. He'll still keep playing a problem
That was the greatest song of the night. Oh, he's fine, right
Yeah, so I got oceans the oceans the woo there hack rate studios and everyone subscribe to these by the way or just go to
They're not wait. What was the last one?
That is
That's a joke dude. You mute me when I'm rocking out
You're being funny dude, it's so funny dude. You're being loud. You want to play?
Everybody enjoys it. Everybody enjoys it. He was
Nigger nigger nigger
won't you come wash away won't you come won't you come
yeah you're not gonna get banned over that he said digger by the way
Yeah, he was saying that Niger Nadja by the way yesterday on the show like they were trying to make it sound like I typed
NIGER in in Bronzeberg's chat, and then it turns out with somebody else
Thank you, that was really yeah, mr. Bigpipes is kind of mean right? I didn't hear anything
Okay, I'm gonna end this in the stream. I'll be back. Okay. I'll be back. I'll be right back
They docks they slander they gaslight they disrupt
But what if you had the ultimate guide to shut them down?
Introducing trollopedia your field manual to decode
expose, and outsmart internet trolls. From classic tactics like love bombing to modern swarm attacks,
Trollopedia breaks it all down. Know the playbook, flip the script, take back your power. Trollopedia.